(Imagawa) I hope I can get better from now on.
(Asai) Let's stop it.
(Sanada) I'll stop everything NOTE Sanada
(Imagawa) Sanayan (Asai) Sanayan!
(Yamanaka) Sanada?
Because kids these days are a little different.
You complain easily and run away right away, right?
To the person who has been chosen for a long time
There's no way you can understand the feelings of people who aren't always chosen, right?
Well then...
(Kakizaki) Sanada!
(Kakizaki) Look carefully.
Ishida is also a dance beginner like Sanada.
⚟♬ “Shall we dance?” ”
⚟♬～
♬～
Shallow, get the ketchup
Yes (Imagawa) Thank you
♬～
(sound of door opening)
What is it, Nikolai?
♬～
Ah, I don't know anymore, what's wrong?
I can't record something.
I don't know
Hey, Mr. Kakizaki, don't you know much about this kind of thing?
That kind of mechanical work is Sanada's role, right?
Because he's not here anymore.
(Ishida) I will read the instructions.
♬～
(Fukuko) It's not what I said after all.
Sorry, Eternal Boys aims to debut with 5 members NOTE Eternal Boys
Is it really okay?
No problem
Even though I said there was no problem, I decided to withdraw immediately...
yes…
After all, there are no come-from-behind home runs in real life.
♬～
Hey, is it really okay for Sanada to resign?
You're persistent, okay? I don't care.
It seems like they're everywhere... Is that so?
I met him for the first time since I became an adult.
There's no such thing as a lie
Not being able to lie is a drawback in this world.
Isn't that the case with hosts?
Sanada just wasn't for me, that's all.
You're a liar
♬～
After all, why don't we do the actual performance tomorrow?
Why? I took the trouble to fix the camera.
After all, Eternal Boys is Eternal Boys with six members.
Huh? Such an irresponsible person...
What do you think, Mr. Yamanaka? as a manager
I? I...
Let's shoot a video with 5 people
Asai
yes
⚟♬ “Shall we dance?” ”
⚟♬～
Let's continue!
Sorry!
Were you practicing?
yes
Well, today's dance wasn't bad.
sweet
what do you want to do?
If you want to quit, now's the time. No one will blame you.
Me too...
I want to see more scenery with everyone.
Please enter Eternal Boys again.
Understood
Prove in your life that anyone can shine anytime.
yes
Sanayaan! Welcome back!
I'm already a little scared
(Imagawa/Asai) Yay!
Sanayan! Sanayan! Sanayan!
(Suzu Hontsubo) NOTE Suzu Hontsubo
♬～
(Kashiwa hand)
I want my dance video to go viral and sell.
Health and success for participating in idol festivals
I hope Eternal Boys can debut soon.
What about Sanada?
Well...
I'll try my best to become an idol
thank you
That's not a wish hahahaha
♬～
Sanada: It's a big hit. It's the first time I've seen it (Imagawa). Look, look, look...
(Asai) 1 million views, isn't that enough? (Imagawa) shallow
That's because the entertainment industry is too lenient.
♬～
Please watch this come-from-behind home run.
(Imagawa) Wow! (Asai) I'm saying it.
(Imagawa) Wow! (Asai) 100,000 is amazing, isn't it?
Isn't it amazing? Awesome
Everyone, our debut song
The title is "Eternal"
(Imagawa) Here we come!
If the debut song is decided
That's what I should do next.
what? Was everyone doing well?
Thank you for your hard work (Kakizaki) Thank you for your hard work
Thank you for your hard work
(Sound of breathing) The number of views is also quite high.
thank you
Ren: Greetings to everyone (Ren) Yes, President Fukuko.
I am Ren Ukita, a 4th grade elementary school student belonging to Manpuku Entertainment Production NOTE Ukita
Ukita Ren... I've heard something about it.
I mean, I saw the drama yesterday, Tsuki 9, right?
Ren has been in the top of my favorite child actor ranking for 8 consecutive years.
The nation's little boy is our company's genius child actor.
I'm going to ask Ren, my breadwinner, to appear in the music video for "Eternal".
Huh? oh!
Well then, Yamanaka, I have another one, so please take care of me after this.
Okay, good job Ren.
Thank you for your hard work.Thank you for your hard work.
Nice to meet you Ren
what up? I haven't heard it though
Huh? An old man's MV
It's too lame
I'll never come out, huh?
Ren: This is work. (Ren) No, no, absolutely no.
You're not a child anymore.
(Ren) Ah, that's right. Let's have a comedy competition.
A comedy competition? yes
If you can make me laugh with that
It's okay for you to appear in the MV, you really don't care...
Seriously? I'll do it, but is it okay?
We're pretty funny though
Idols also have a lot of trouble behind the scenes.
What were you doing? I was worried
(Imagawa) But what if I give up on this dream now?
I think you'll stop liking me too.
Absolutely... absolutely cool